Barack B-PER
Obama I-PER
is O
the O
president O
of O
the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

Donald B-PER
Trump I-PER
is O
the O
president O
of O
the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC